[
    {
        "question": "My son ............ football and tennis in the club.",
        "choices": [
            "play",
            "plays",
            "is played",
            "are played"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "plays"
    },
    {
        "question": "My sons ............ football and tennis in the club.",
        "choices": [
            "play",
            "plays",
            "is played",
            "are played"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "are played"
    },
    {
        "question": "Football and tennis ............ in the club.",
        "choices": [
            "play",
            "plays",
            "is played",
            "are played"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "are played"
    },
    {
        "question": "Football ............ in the club.",
        "choices": [
            "play",
            "plays",
            "is played",
            "are played"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "plays"
    },
    {
        "question": "These trees ............ their leaves in autumn.",
        "choices": [
            "isn't lost",
            "don't lose",
            "doesn't lose",
            "aren't lost"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "don't lose"
    },
    {
        "question": "This tree ............ its leaves in autumn.",
        "choices": [
            "isn't lost",
            "don't lose",
            "doesn't lose",
            "aren't lost"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "doesn't lose"
    },
    {
        "question": "The leaves of this tree ............ in autumn.",
        "choices": [
            "isn't lost",
            "don't lose",
            "doesn't lose",
            "aren't lost"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "aren't lost"
    },
    {
        "question": "This tree ............ its leaves in autumn.",
        "choices": [
            "never loses",
            "don't lose",
            "never lose",
            "aren't lost"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "never loses"
    },
    {
        "question": "Does Amir ............ your birthday parties?",
        "choices": [
            "attend",
            "attends",
            "is attended",
            "attending"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "attends"
    },
    {
        "question": "............ you with your homework?",
        "choices": [
            "Anyone helps",
            "Is anyone helped",
            "Does anyone help",
            "Anyone is helped"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Does anyone help"
    },
    {
        "question": "........... with your homework?",
        "choices": [
            "You help",
            "Do you help",
            "You are helped",
            "Are you helped"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Do you help"
    },
    {
        "question": "We ............ a nice time by the sea.",
        "choices": [
            "are had",
            "have",
            "are spent",
            "is spent"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "have"
    },
    {
        "question": "A nice time ............ by the sea.",
        "choices": [
            "are had",
            "have",
            "are spent",
            "is spent"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "is spent"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ali ............ at home right now. He's at school.",
        "choices": [
            "is",
            "doesn't be",
            "isn't",
            "has"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "isn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "A: ............ at home right now? B: No, he's at school.",
        "choices": [
            "Is Ali",
            "Does Ali be",
            "Ali is",
            "Does Ali have"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Is Ali"
    },
    {
        "question": "We ............ lunch before my father returns home.",
        "choices": [
            "haven't",
            "don't have",
            "aren't",
            "don't be"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "don't have"
    },
    {
        "question": "............. lunch before your father returns home?",
        "choices": [
            "You have",
            "Have you",
            "Are you",
            "Do you have"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Have you"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lions ............ meat.",
        "choices": [
            "eats",
            "eat",
            "don't eat",
            "are eaten"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "eat"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lions ............ grass.",
        "choices": [
            "eats",
            "eat",
            "don't eat",
            "are eaten"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "are eaten"
    },
    {
        "question": "This soup ............ very good.",
        "choices": [
            "tastes",
            "taste",
            "is tasting",
            "to taste"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "tastes"
    },
    {
        "question": "My father ............ in a big company. He is an accountant there.",
        "choices": [
            "works",
            "work",
            "is working",
            "is worked"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "works"
    },
    {
        "question": "After I ............ my lunch, I will take a short rest.",
        "choices": [
            "will have",
            "have",
            "had",
            "had had"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "have"
    },
    {
        "question": "I will take a taxi if I ............ up late.",
        "choices": [
            "will get",
            "had got",
            "got",
            "get"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "get"
    },
    {
        "question": "She 'll help you as soon as she ............ her work.",
        "choices": [
            "will finish",
            "finish",
            "finishes",
            "have finished"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "finishes"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the timetable, the train ............ the station at seven.",
        "choices": [
            "will reach",
            "had reached",
            "reach",
            "reaches"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "reaches"
    },
    {
        "question": "My father works as a doctor. He ............ very busy examining patients.",
        "choices": [
            "often is",
            "is often",
            "often has",
            "has often"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "is often"
    },
    {
        "question": "Leen ............ something to do. She is very busy.",
        "choices": [
            "always have",
            "have always",
            "always has",
            "has always"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "has always"
    },
    {
        "question": "I visit my grandparents ............ month, in the beginning and in the middle.",
        "choices": [
            "twice",
            "once",
            "once a",
            "twice a"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "once a"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sama is used ............ in Aswan.",
        "choices": [
            "to living",
            "alive",
            "to live",
            "living"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "living"
    },
    {
        "question": "It is Omar's habit ............ for walks on Fridays.",
        "choices": [
            "going",
            "to going",
            "to go",
            "goes"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hussein ............ working on the farm.",
        "choices": [
            "is used",
            "is used to",
            "used to",
            "used"
        ]
    }
]